本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组 原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址 http://shinybbs.com
翻译： Susu Yatamisaki VirusKiller
校对|后期： 唱唱反调
接下来是你上周错过的《无耻之徒》的剧情
This is what you miss last week on "Shamless"
看看就知道怎么回事了
Well, just watch the screen, you'll get it
我一直在看关于这个父女贞洁舞会的资料
I've been reading more about this Purity Ball thing.
"让你再次如处女般纯洁"
"re-dedicate yourself as a virgin."
承认你的罪过
confess your transgressions,
我就把车给你
I'll give you the damn car.
你得勇敢面对他 卡什
You have to stand up to him, Kash.
放回去
Put it back.
快点
Now.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
只是吃了你一块士力架而已啊
It's a fucking Snickers bar!
我给她买了套房子
I bought her a house.
到时候你就跟史蒂夫住到隔壁
You'll be living with Steve
他给你买的房子里了
in that house he bought next door!
带我去看房子吧
Show me the house.
我喜欢你 菲奥娜
I like you, Fiona.
你还记得史蒂夫吗
You remember Steve?
当然 最近怎么样啊
Yeah. How's it going?
我只需要你和莫妮卡的签名
All I need is your signature and Monica's,
然后钱就是你的了
and the money is all yours.
莫妮卡在希莉娅家
Monica's over at Sheila's.
这个莫妮卡到底是谁啊
Who the hell is Monica?
她妈妈
Her mother.
我的天呐
Oh my god.
莫妮在你想让她签的破文件签字
How about Moni sign whatever the hell it is you need...
- 然后利亚姆归我们 - 成交
- we get Liam. - Done.
你不能抛弃了你的孩子
You don't get to abandon your kids
然后有一天突然出现择优挑走一个
and then show up one day to take your pick of the litter.
我和萝贝塔想组建自己的家庭
Roberta and I want to start a family of our own.
既然你都在这儿了
You're here now.
那就没我什么事儿了
I'm done.
无耻之徒 美版 第一季第10集
# 想想过去拥有的幸运 #
Think of all the luck you got
# 深知非镜花水月 #
Know that it's not for naught
# 你也曾光芒四射 #
You were beaming once before
# 但已一去不返 #
But it's not like that anymore
# 现在的落魄 #
What is this downside
# 何以形容 #
That you speak of
# 还有什么感受你是确信的 #
What is this feeling you're so sure of
# 三五好友小聚 #
Round up the friends you got
# 深知他们非镜花水月 #
Know that they're not for naught
# 你也曾乐此不疲 #
You were willing once before
# 但已一去不返 #
But it's not like that anymore
# 现在的落魄 #
What is this downside
# 何以形容 #
That you speak of
# 还有什么感受 #
What is this feeling
# 你是确... 信的 #
You're so... sure of
你打算在这儿过家家到什么时候
So how long you plan on us staying here playing house?
你没有看到孩子们的脸吗
Did you see those kids' faces?
你没有注意到他们看我的表情吗
Do you see the way they looked at me?
我可不要养六个孩子
I'm not supporting six kids.
等明天我们拿到DNA测试的结果
We get the DNA results tomorrow.
就能证明利亚姆不是弗兰克的孩子了
It'll prove Liam's not Frank's.
这样的话 如果那个白痴改了主意
That way if this shithead changes his mind,
- 他就无法把利亚姆要回去了 - 小声点
- he can't ever try and take Liam back. - Quiet.
小声点 他们都睡了
Quiet. They're sleeping.
亲爱的 我们会成为快乐的一家人的
We are going to make a great family, baby.
我会照顾你和利亚姆
I'm going to take care of you and Liam
比弗兰克好一万倍
like Frank never could.
孩子是你的 法院绝对判给你
Possession is 9/10th's of the law.
太安静了
It's so quiet.
这样不是很好吗
It's nice, right?
是啊
Yeah.
肯定是E-6
It has to be E-6.
那是唯一一个能放下航空母舰的格子
It's the only spot left big enough for a carrier.
不 不对...
No, it's not...
莫妮卡都没给他们讲睡前故事
Monica didn't even bother to read to them
不给他们掖被子
or tuck them in.
她说不定都忘了给利亚姆涂屁屁霜呢
She probably forgot to use Liam's ass cream, too.
就是这样的
Yes, it is.
- 你又作弊 - 不 我没有
- You're cheating again! - No, I'm not!
卡尔 回你的房间去
Carl, go back to your room.
黛比  上床睡觉
Debbie, go to sleep.
- 明天还要上学呢 - 我们马上就完了
- School tomorrow. - We're almost done.
你们俩刷牙了吗
You both brush your teeth?
刷了
Yes...!
卡尔
Carl?
快去 现在就去
Go. Now.
晚安 卡尔
Night, Carl.
晚安 菲奥娜 爱你
Night, Fiona. Love you.
- 爱你 菲奥娜 - 我也爱你
- Love you, Fiona. - Love you, too.
不许在被子里看书
And no reading under the covers.
莫妮卡 卡尔需要你帮忙
Monica, Carl needs something from you.
- 给 - 什么 这是什么
- Here. - What? What's this?
知情同意书
Permission slip.
你要去水族馆啦
Oh. You're going to the aquarium!
- 什么时候 - 今天
- When? - Today.
- 我需要十块钱 - 干什么用
- I need ten dollars. - What for?
买门票
Admission fee.
学校不管门票吗
School doesn't pay for that?
不管 他还需要午餐钱呢
No, and he'll need money for food.
给他弄点速溶面片加一块果酱馅饼
Grab him an instant oatmeal and a Pop-Tart.
就是很好的午餐了
Makes a great lunch.
小黛 你在干吗
Deb, what are you doing?
我在找硬纸板和记号笔
I'm looking for a poster board and markers.
我要准备再次竞选
I'm running for re-election.
伊恩 你能帮帮她吗
Ian, could you help her?
如果你们昨晚就告诉我这些事
If you all would tell me these things the night before,
我今天早上就不会这么手忙脚乱的了
it would be a little better in the morning.
- 我需要四十块钱 - 不行
- I need 40 bucks. - No.
鲍比 你有五块吗
Bob, do you have a five?
在我钱包里有
In... in my wallet.
谁也别想拿走
Where it's gonna stay.
我要买一本微积分的新课本
Look, I need a new calculus textbook.
我可以弄本二手的 二十块就够了
I can get it used; only costs 20.
我们的午餐呢
Where are our lunches?
你们看什么看啊
What is everybody looking at?
赶紧动手往面包上抹花生酱吧
Start spreading peanut butter on bread.
对
Right.
好了
So...
花生酱在哪儿
Okay. Where's the jelly?
操蛋的莫妮卡
Fucking Monica.
她连鸡蛋都不会做
She can barely cook an egg.
她都没给他们准备午餐
She didn't even make them lunches.
现在她又要害他们上学迟到了
Now she's got them leaving for school late
而那个黑胖子拉拉就坐在那儿啥也不干
while that fat lesbian sits on her ass doing nothing.
行了 屋里冻死了
All right. It's freezing in here.
过去帮他们一把吧
Go over and help out.
- 她去死吧 - 她快把你搞疯了
- Fuck her! - She's driving you crazy.
- 我很好 - 好吧 那就是我快被搞疯了
- I'm fine. - All right, then it's driving me crazy.
相信我 我早晚会回去的
Believe me, I'll be back over there soon enough.
你昨晚上睡觉了吗
You get any sleep last night?
她把卡尔留在十月节直到十一月
She left Carl at Oktoberfest until November.
就是这个女人
This is a woman
一边抽烟一边照顾利亚姆
who burned a hole in Liam's footie pajamas
后来睡着了 还把他的睡衣烧了个洞
when she fell asleep smoking while nursing.
- 她回来了 - 她不管不顾 好吗
- She came back. - She's a flake. Okay?
她从来不打电话
She never called.
她也不来看我们
She never came by.
也从来没给孩子们寄过哪怕一张生日卡
She never sent those kids a fucking birthday card!
她刚走那会儿一定很难熬吧
Must've been hard when she left.
- 孩子们心都快碎了 - 我是说你
- Destroyed the kids. - I meant you.
我可是喜极而泣啊
I wept tears of joy.
我们需要一张沙发
We need a couch.
你应该找个律师
You should talk to a lawyer.
是啊
Oh, right.
我连饭都吃不饱
I can't keep food on the table,
还要请个律师
but I'm hiring a lawyer.
去搞清楚莫妮卡有什么权利
Just to find out what Monica can and can't do.
好了 我得去工作了
Here, you know what? I gotta get to work.
- 接着 - 什...
- Hup! Catch! - Wha...?
- 这是什么 - 你的新手机
- What's this? - Your own cell phone.
我跟你说过我不要你给我买东西
I told you I don't want you buying me stuff.
但情侣们都这样啊
It's what couples do.
给我们买张沙发吧
Get us a couch.
好了
Okay. Um...
完成了
Okay!
拿着吧
Everyone...
等你们放学回来的时候我们不会在家
We won't be here when you get home from school.
- 为什么 - 怎么了
- Why? - What?
菲奥娜总是告诉我们原因的
Fiona always tells us why.
- 关你们什么屁事 - 鲍比
- None of your damn business why. - Bob!
你妈妈让你们去上学 所以赶紧去吧
Your mother told you to go, so go!
- 走吧 - 你们先走 我随后就到
- Out. - Go on, guys. I'll catch up.
拜拜
Bye. Bye.
我他妈才不管DNA测试结果是什么
I don't care what the fucking DNA test says.
你们不能带走利亚姆
You're not taking Liam.
我们走着瞧
We'll see about that.
啊 走着瞧
Yeah, we will.
你有问题吗
Are we having a problem,
菲利普
Phillip?!
我不知道啊 鲍比
I dunno... Bob!
咱说说 你跑到我家来安营扎寨
Let's see. You're camped out in my house,
你上我妈妈
you're fucking my mother,
现在你还在盘算着怎么偷走我小弟
and you're talking about stealing my baby brother.
你说我们有没有问题
Why would we have a problem?
- 小子 小心我揍你 - 停下 别说了
- Boy, I will kick your... - Stop it! Hey!
恭喜你啊 老妈
And congratulations, Mom.
你择偶的眼光还是一如既往的不错
You always knew how to pick 'em.
利普
Lip!
别走
Please stop!
求你了
Please!
我们还没好好说句话呢
We haven't had a chance to talk.
还有什么好谈的
Don't worry about it.
我想谈谈
No, I do.
我 天呐
I... Oh, geez.
我不知道从哪儿说起
I don't know where to start.
怎么向你解释
How to explain.
我一直担心你
I worry about you.
我无时无刻不在想你
I think about you all the time.
我很想你
I miss you.
我有那么多问题想问你
There's so much I want to ask you.
学校怎么样
How's school?
你一直都那么聪明
You were always so smart.
我的利普
My Lip.
我知道你无所不能
I know you can do anything.
对不起我伤害了你
I'm so sorry I hurt you.
看着我
Oh, look at me.
下次你想回家来看看
Next time you're thinking about dropping in,
就免了吧
don't.
你已经把我们祸害得够惨了
You've fucked up our lives enough already.
豪克马电台这周末
Touched By An Angel marathon
"天使的触碰"大联播
on the Hallmark Channel this weekend.
我一直挺喜欢那个的
Ooh, I always liked that one. Mm-hmm.
除了那位爱尔兰女士 她好奇怪
Except the Irish lady. She's weird.
TBS也要联播"硝烟"
Gunsmoke marathon on TBS, too.
你说我们能给它喷漆吗
Think we could get it painted?
- 我说车 - 你想怎样都行 我的小公主
- The car. - Anything you want, Princess.
我很骄傲 你居然决定参加
I am just so proud of you for deciding to go to
贞洁舞会 让我以上帝希望的方式
the Purity Ball and letting me protect you
来保护你
the way Jesus intended, huh?
- 上学愉快 亲爱的 - 拜拜 妈妈
- Have fun at school, sweetie. - Bye, Mom.
弗兰克
Frank.
我做了山莓馅的比利时煎饼
I made Belgian crepes with raspberries,
还给你浇了点枫糖浆
and there's a little maple syrup for you.
没时间吃了 我要迟到了
Uh, can't. I'm late.
你要去哪儿
Where you going?
我跟你说了
I told you.
我要去接上莫妮卡 然后去市政办公室
I'm picking up Monica, going to the city clerk's office,
签好和解书 拿到那笔钱
signing the settlement and getting the money.
那个... 莫妮卡
So... Monica?
对 莫妮卡
Yes, Monica.
你也想让我得到那笔钱 不是吗
You want me to get the money, don't you?
这是唯一的原因吗
Is that the only reason?
- 当然 - 弗兰克
- Yes. - Frank?
你晚上回来吃饭吗
Are you coming home for dinner?
- 当然回来吃 - 确定吗
- Absolutely. - You sure?
对 确定 我要迟到了
Yes, Yes. I'm late.
要迟到了
I'm late.
操
Fuck.
谢天谢地我们明天就走了
Thank God we're leaving tomorrow.
- 我觉得我不能走 - 不 你可以的
- I don't think I can. - Yes, you can.
孩子们需要我
These kids need me.
他们能照顾好自己的
They're fine.
你没看见利普的样子吗 他多伤心啊
You didn't see Lip? How brokenhearted he was?
亲爱的 过一阵子他就没事了
Oh, honey, he'll get over it.
我们不能把利亚姆从他哥哥姐姐们身边带走
We can't take Liam from his brothers and sisters.
他要跟我们一起走
He's coming with us.
不 这是上天给我的预示
No. The universe is giving me a sign.
给了我机会成为理想中的那个母亲
An opportunity to be the mother I never could be.
离开这群孩子我一直很愧疚
I always felt guilty about leaving those kids.
我现在好多了 我觉得我能做到
I'm-I'm better now. I think I can handle it.
是的
Yeah.
看着我
Look at me.
莫妮卡 听着
Monica! Look... Uh-uh.
看着我
Look at me.
我们相遇的时候 你就像只丧家犬
When we met, you were like a beaten dog,
命悬一线
barely hanging on by a thread.
我现在坚强多了
I am stronger now.
如果我们留下来 你能撑多久呢 宝贝
But for how long if we stay here, baby?
能撑多久
For how long, hmm?
我们拿到DNA结果
We're getting the DNA results, then
就带上利亚姆离开这里
we're leaving with Liam.
哎哟
Oh-ho.
希望我没有打扰你们的睡衣派对 莫妮
I hope I'm not interrupting a pajama party, Moni.
这就是你们这俩娘们儿常在一起干的事 对吗
That's what you ladies do when you're together, right?
枕头大战之类的
Pillow fights and the like?
你倒希望有个跟我的一样大的老二
You wish you had a dick as big as mine.
我的那条可是又粗又长
I am a man of ample girth and length.
不信你问莫妮
Ask Moni.
如果你觉得隔着牛仔裤看不出什么
If I seem unimpressive in my Wranglers, it's because
那是因为我不喜炫耀 膨胀取胜
I'm a grower, not a shower.
不过相信我
But trust me,
如果需要大展拳脚的话 我那可生机勃勃
when it's time to show, I grow.
来吧 盖夫人
Come on, Mrs. G.
我们开路吧
Let's hit the road.
老弗的钞票就要到手了
Frankie's got some moolah coming his way.
计划有变 老弗
Change of plans, Frankie.
除非你征得利普 菲奥娜和孩子们的同意
Monica's not signing those papers
让我们带走利亚姆
until you get Lip, Fiona and
否则莫妮卡是不会签字的
the kids on board with us taking Liam.
什么
What?
莫妮卡得确定孩子们不会恨她
Monica needs to know that the kids aren't going to hate her.
太迟了 他们早就恨她入骨了
It's too late. They already hate her.
别逼我们 弗兰克
Don't push it, Frank.
我们可本来能索取
We could be asking
离婚赡养费以及你那一半的赔偿费
for the spousal support and half the settlement money.
算你狠
Fine.
菲奥娜在哪
Where's Fiona?
隔壁
Next door.
她搬去和史蒂夫一起住了
She moved in with Steve.
史蒂夫是哪个傻逼
Who the fuck is Steve?
天啊
Oh, God...
今年又来这一套 贾斯珀
That time of the year again, Jasper?
是啊 就像每年都要过圣诞一样 弗兰克
Yeah, just like Christmas, Frank.
我知道你很狡猾
I know you've been naughty.
别跟着我
Stop following me.
我这还有摄像机呢
Got my camcorder right here.
抓到你的把柄只是时间的问题
Just a matter of time before I catch you.
滚远点
Fuck off.
米奇怎么样了
How's Mickey doing?
还被他们关在县里的监狱里
They still have him at the jail ward over at County.
你去探望过他了吗
You been over to visit him?
没有
Nah.
那帮女同性恋狱警搜个身
Those dyke guards pat you down
简直就像二把刀妇产医生
like amateur gynecologists.
卡什呢
How's Kash?
几个邻居监管大妈跑到店里来
Couple of the Neighborhood Watch ladies
想给他办游行致敬
came by the store, offered to throw him a parade.
卡什最好趁米奇出来之前
Kash had better move his family back to Baghdad
把家迁回巴格达
before Mickey gets out.
他来自埃文斯顿
He's from Evanston.
还不是好远嘛
Won't be nearly far enough.
曼蒂...
Mandy...
利普
Lip.
搭配得挺不错
It's a nice outfit.
这是什么风格 海盗少妇风吗
What is that... uh, pirate wench?
喜欢吗
You like?
你第三节什么课
What's your third period?
健康课
Health.
怎么了
Why?
我们得逃几节课
Think we need to miss some school.
回见
See you.
托尼
Tony?
有人买了哈里森先生的房子吗
Somebody bought Mr. Harris' house?
窗户上的钉板没了
Windows aren't boarded up anymore.
是啊 有人买了
Yeah. Somebody did.
谁
Who?
史蒂夫
Steve.
是吗
Yeah.
希望他放放味儿
Hope he can get the smell out.
哈里森的尸体在厕所烂了好久
Harris was dead on the toilet a long time
才被我们发现
before we found him.
他那是几个意思
What was that about?
走吧
Come on.
- 你能行吗 - 妈的
- You're good? - Shit!
小心点 小心点
Careful, careful, careful, careful.
- 等等 - 噢 - 我抓住了 我抓住了
- Stop it! - Ow! - I got it. I got it.
好啊 我们可是女汉子
Okay, girl power.
放 放 放
And down, down, down, down, down, down, down.
- 噢 - 噢 对不起
- Oh. - Oh. Oh, sorry.
沙发真漂亮
Nice couch.
搞什么鬼啊 弗兰克
What the hell, Frank?
史蒂夫需要新锁了
Steve needs new locks.
- 你私闯民宅 - 和男朋友同居了啊
- You broke in? - Living with the boyfriend.
- 什么 - 她不肯签协议
- What? - She won't sign my settlement
除非你和孩子们不阻挠她们带走利亚姆
until you and the kids stop harassing her over Liam.
我们没有阻挠她
We're not harassing her.
孩子需要跟妈妈在一起
The boy needs to be with his mother.
他现在和他妈妈在一起 除非她决定再跑一次
He is with his mother till she decides to take off again.
你明显不在乎这些啊
You obviously don't care.
你都搬进了这间爱巢
You've moved into this love nest.
我没有搬
I didn't move.
在你的老婆滚蛋之前 我暂住在这儿
I'm staying here until your wife fucks up.
你妈妈和我怎么安排
What your mother and I decide to do
我们的儿子利亚姆 是我们的事 菲奥娜
with our son Liam is our business, Fiona,
与你无关
not yours.
我一定要拿到那笔钱
I am getting that money!
所以呢
So?
我觉得他可能是来真的
I think he might be serious.
- 嗨 弗兰克 - 闭嘴
- Hey, Frank. - Fuck!
哟 弗兰克
Yo, Frank.
希莉娅来了个电话 说"正在做你最爱的晚餐
Sheila called and "is making your favorite dinner...
炖牛肉"
pot roast."
希莉娅给你做了炖牛肉
Sheila's making you pot roast?
噢 真是恩爱啊
Oh, that's so sweet.
噢 还有 贾斯珀又跑过来转了一圈
Oh, and hey, that Jasper guy was hanging around again,
问了些关于你的问题
asking questions about you.
- 噢 - 想知道你现在什么情况
- Aah! - Wanted to know how you felt.
是不是回去工作了 还有一些乱七八糟的事
If you were back to work, that sort of thing.
那帮该死的残协的人
Fucking disability guy.
他就在外面
He's outside right now.
整个早上都在跟踪我
Been following me around all morning.
我告诉他你在苦练马拉松
I told him you were training for a marathon.
每年那个傻逼
Every year that shithead
都来挑我的刺 想停了我的残障补贴
tries to trip me up, stop my disability check.
我最近终于时来运转
I finally get some luck,
那个傻逼又带了台摄像机来搞我
and this douche with a video cam has to show up.
你可从没走过运
You don't have any luck.
谁说的
Hello!
理赔的钱 谢谢
Settlement money. Thank you.
除非我能
If I can get
让莫妮卡远离那个男人婆
Monica away from Rosie Greer long enough
就能签那个狗屁玩意儿
to sign the goddamn thing!
我猜 鲍比不会让莫妮卡离开她的视线的
Yeah, well, my guess... Bob won't let Monica out of her sight.
她还是很漂亮 不是吗
She did look beautiful, though, didn't she?
保养的那么好
Really keeping herself up.
好吧 那什么
Yeah, what about, uh,
希莉娅和炖牛肉怎么办
Sheila and the pot roast?
她就像口腔溃疡一样...
She's like mouth herpes... the gift
花样层出不穷
that keeps on giving.
她不适合 莫妮卡才是我的灵魂伴侣
No. Monica is my soul mate.
我们很合得来
We just click.
家里有一对同性恋而且还能拿到一笔钱
Two lesbians at home and the promise of cash.
也许你真的转运了 弗兰克
Maybe your luck has changed, Frank.
不
Nah.
我们要查些什么
What are we looking for?
怎么推翻父母的权利
How to override parental rights.
我们是找儿童与家庭服务部还是律师
We thinking DCFS or attorneys?
律师
Attorneys.
我一到十八岁就该这么做的
I should have done this when I turned 18.
莫妮卡走了之后弗兰克就跟丢了魂一样
Frank was so broken after Monica left,
他什么都会签的
he would have signed anything.
这有个人选
Here's someone.
马克雷戴尔
Mark Rydell.
你无法为自己战斗时
He'll fight for you
他会挺身而出
when you can't fight for yourself.
亚裔牛仔 算了吧
Asian cowboy? Don't think so.
那个女的怎么样
Oh, what about that lady?
在高山赌场弗兰克把卡尔和黛比 锁在车里
The one that helped get Carl and Debbie back
是她把他们找回了
when Frank locked them in that car at Indian bingo.
米莎戴维斯
Micha Davis.
这就是她
Is this her?
看起来她好像刚拉到裤子里了
Looks like she just shit in her pants.
再找找
Keep looking.
啊
Ah.
这个怎么样 克莉丝汀道林
There's one. Christine Dowling.
长得不错 还很专业
Attractive, professional...
而且看起来她真有法律学位
And she looks like she might actually have a law degree.
给她打个电话
Let's call her.
你哪儿来的车
Where'd you get the car?
从史蒂夫那借的
Borrowed it from Steve.
和他干了点事儿
Been working with him a bit.
干了什么
Doing what?
还是别让菲奥娜知道的好
Oh, better not let Fiona find out about it,
否则她会杀了你... 还有他
or she'll kill you... and him.
你还好吗
You doing okay?
好多烦心事
Lot going on.
好吧 是因为莫妮卡回来了吧
Yeah. It's weird having Monica back.
是啊 那也算一部分
Yeah. Yeah, that, too.
什么 还有别的
What? Something else?
一言难尽
It's kind of hard to explain.
和我说说吧
Try me.
米奇也是个同性恋 我们还做过了
Mickey's gay, and we're doing it.
而卡什因为我才对米奇开枪的
And Kash shot Mickey because of me,
可是米奇宁愿去少管所也不愿承认他是同性恋
but Mickey would rather go to juvie than admit he's gay.
所以 我和卡什还有米奇都干过了
So, I'm doing both Kash and Mickey.
噢 最近和卡什没怎么做过
Well, not so much Kash lately.
不过我和卡什打得火热那会儿
But when Kash and me were hot and heavy,
被琳达发现了
Linda found out about it,
然后她强迫卡什给她再生个孩子
and is blackmailing Kash into having another kid.
一团糟啊
Holy shit.
是啊
Yeah.
她们出来了
Here they come.
我打算今天去见见他
I think I'm gonna go see him today.
谁 卡什
Who? Kash?
不 米奇
No. Mickey.
他在监狱等着判决
He's in jail awaiting sentencing.
我想知道我要怎么才能
I want to know what I have to do to adopt
收养我年幼的弟弟以及其他的兄弟姐妹
my toddler brother and possibly my other siblings, as well,
尽可能的靠自己抚养他们
and raise them as my own.
你们的父母还健在吗
Are both your parents still alive?
- 是的 - 不称职吗
- Yes. - Incompetent?
非常不称职
Very.
好吧 你是在说
Okay, well, you're talking about
想撤销他们的监护权
vacating their parental rights and becoming
然后成为几个孩子的合法监护人来着
legal guardian of how many?
五个
Five.
噢 那还真是多啊
Oh, that's a lot of kids.
你要知道 法律中有关亲权的部分
You know, the law's pretty strict
是相当严格的
regarding parental rights.
你得证明他们的不称职
You'd need to prove incompetence.
你有确凿的证据吗
Do you have a case?
你有多少时间
How much time do you have?
我有一个文件夹
I have a folder.
你有一个文件夹 好吧
You got a folder. Okay.
看起来你的母亲...
Well, it looks like your mother...
莫妮卡
Monica.
莫妮卡几年前离开了
...Monica left a couple of years ago?
二十一个半月
21 and a half months.
她现在回来了吗
Is she back now?
算是吧
Sort of.
还有你的父亲
And your father,
弗兰克盖拉格
Frank Gallagher...
哇 他的事情可真不少
Wow. He's a live one.
酒鬼一个
Drinker?
对
Yeah.
你挣的钱
Uh, do you make
能达到六个人家庭的联邦贫困线吗
federal poverty level wages for a family of six?
那是多少钱
How much is that?
一年大约三万吧
30 grand a year or so.
所以说 你挣的钱不足以赡养他们
So you don't earn enough money to support them,
而且我们还得证明你的父母不称职
and we'd have to prove your parents incompetent?
听着 我知道这很烦人
Listen, I know it bites the big one,
但最好的结果就是
but the best case scenario
在你和你父亲争夺抚养权的时候
is the county places your brothers and sisters
郡县把你的弟弟妹妹
in foster care
送到寄养家庭照看
while you and your father fight over custody.
- 盖拉格女士 - 在这儿
- Mrs. Gallagher? - Yeah.
- 谢谢你 - 不客气
- Thank you. - Yeah.
他是弗兰克的孩子
He's Frank's.
什么
What?!
弗兰克是他的父亲
Frank's the father.
这他妈怎么可能
How the fuck is this possible?
我不知道
I don't know.
我一直以为我是在斑马酒吧
I always thought I got pregnant
和那个酒保嗑药时怀的
when I did E with that bouncer at the Zebra Lounge.
我醒来时一丝不挂
I-I woke up naked.
法律还是站在我们这一边的
The law's still on our side.
什么
What?
你是母亲
You're the mother.
对
Yeah.
那么我们今天找到弗兰克
So, we find Frank today,
告诉他我们会签署他的协议
tell him we'll sign his settlement papers
以换取他的抚养权
in exchange for him signing over his parental rights.
在那之后
After that,
菲奥娜无能为力了
there ain't a damn thing Fiona can do about it.
我们走 莫妮卡
Come on, Monica.
不能让他毁了我的家庭
He's not ruining my fucking family.
我向上帝发誓
I swear to God,
他休想把儿子从我身边带走
he's not going to take my son away from me.
操他大爷
Fucking the shit!
哇
Wow.
她们看起来挺不高兴的
They look unhappy.
是啊
Yeah.
刚才走的那两个女人
Two women who just left
一定是对结果不满意啊 是吧
must not have not been happy with the news they got, huh?
对 这经常发生
Oh, yeah. Happens.
上个月有一个家伙
Had a guy last month
甚至在男厕所上吊了
hang himself from a pipe in the men's room.
那么 需要我帮忙吗
So, can I help you?
嗯 我想...
Yeah, uh, I think, uh...
我想或许你能帮的上忙
I think maybe you can.
你还要这样做多久 贾斯珀
How long you gonna keep this up, Jasper?
需要多久就多久
Well, as long as it takes this time.
保险公司已经不想再付钱给你了
Insurer is sick and tired of paying you.
他们知道你是装的
They know you're faking.
我要能证明 他们会付我一千元
Gonna pay me a thousand bucks for proving it.
嘿 贾斯珀
Hey, Jasper.
莫妮卡
Monica!
你在吗
You here?
我跟菲奥娜谈过了
I talked to Fiona!
都妥了
Everything's good!
莫妮卡
Monica!
菲奥娜在哪呢
Where's Fiona?
她已经不住这儿了
Doesn't live here anymore.
莫妮卡呢
Monica?
也不在
Nope.
我觉得我把胳膊摔断了
I think I broke my arm.
巨疼
It hurts a lot.
知道了
Yeah.
- 那一条胳膊 - 对
- That one? - Yeah.
啊 搞什么
Ow! What the...?!
去拿你的自行车
Go get your bike.
你确定你准备好了
You sure you're ready for this?
当然了
Hell, yeah.
我是说 仅仅因为利亚姆是弗兰克的孩子
I mean, just 'cause Liam's Frank's
这不代表我们这几个人都是
doesn't mean the rest of us are.
对
Yeah.
好了 这里写着
All right, it says here
我们要做的就是
all we have to do is...
在自己脸颊内侧上刮一下 然后把它送回去
swab our own cheeks and send it back in.
对 还得每人付一百五十美元
Yeah, and pay them 150 bucks each.
我们有微小的希望和弗兰克没有血缘关系
On the off chance we're not related to Frank,
这是完全值得的
it's totally worth it.
张开嘴
Open up.
实际上这挺酷的
It's actually pretty cool...
这里面有很多东西
there's a lot of shit
可以让我们清楚地了解自己
we can figure out about ourselves in there.
对 比如我们是不是继承了弗兰克的酗酒基因
Yeah, like, uh, if we got the alcoholic gene from Frank.
是啊 或是莫妮卡的笨蛋基因
Yeah, or the dummy gene from Monica.
或者我们之中是否有人会成为同性恋
Or if any of us is gonna turn out to be gay.
真不错
Nice.
就现在
Now!
卡尔
Carl!
卡尔 哦
Carl. Oh...
我觉得你撞断了他的胳膊
I think you broke his arm.
哦 糟糕
Oh, shit!
我现在能去医院了吗
Can I go to the hospital now?
先给我几声惨叫
Just give me a couple of more yells first.
哦 我的孩子
Oh, my boy!
那烤肉闻起来棒极了
That roast smells amazing.
别打它的算盘了 那不是给你的
Don't get any ideas, it's not for you.
弗兰克不会回来了 他和他的妻子在一起呢
Frank's not coming back. He's with his wife now.
我知道没人在这儿吃你做的美味
I know how disappointed you get
有多么令你沮丧
when nobody's here to eat your wonderful meals.
妈妈
Mom!
我的连衣裙在哪里
Where is my dress?
来吧 宝贝
Come on, sweet girl.
太棒了 好的...
It's so good. Okay...
太完美了
Perfect.
- 好了 让我把侧边拉链拉上 - 好的
- Okay, let me get the side zipper. - Okay.
你看起来很漂亮
You look beautiful.
我的天呐
My goodness.
你...你看起来美极了
You... you look stunning.
我太为你自豪了
I am so proud of you.
好了 埃迪
All right, Eddie.
不如在去父女纯洁舞会之前
Why don't you just join us for dinner
和我们一起吃晚餐吧
before you both go to the Purity Ball?
你确定吗
You're sure?
我...给弗兰克留点菜就好了
I'll just...save a plate for Frank.
谢谢你给我的物资供应帐户充了钱
Thanks for putting money in my commissary account.
美国监狱中有专门想犯人出售日常生活用品的商定
我的烟快不够抽的了
I was running low on smokes.
不是我 是卡什充的钱
Not me. Kash.
我告诉他你可能还会上诉
I told him you might still press charges.
谢谢了
Thanks.
判多久
How long?
我不知道 应该是一年吧
I don't know. Supposed to be a year, right?
如果我不做傻事的话可能只有几个月
Maybe only a couple months if I don't do anything stupid.
比如什么
Like what?
比如捅死那个
Like stab that fat
一直想偷我果冻的肥猪
fuckin' mick who keeps trying to steal my Jell-O!
- 说谁呢 我 - 就是你
- Who? Me? - Yeah!
去你的
Fuck you!
我...我想你了
I, I miss you.
你再说一次
You say that again,
我就把你的舌头扯下来
I'll rip your tongue out of your head.
- 把你的手从玻璃上拿开 - 哦
- Take your hand off the glass. - Oh.
晚上好 警官 没什么事吧
Good evening, Officer. Is everything okay?
我不知道 有事吗
I don't know. Is it?
哦 嘿 托尼 你怎么样
Oh. Hey. Tony, how you doing?
很好
Good.
那么...我做错什么事了吗
So... did I do something wrong?
尾灯灭了吗
Taillight out?
胎压太低了吗
Low tire?
不不不 祝贺你买了新房子
No, no, no, uh, congratulations on the new house.
哦对
Yeah.
对 在那一片还算不错的房子
Yeah, yeah, nice little fixer-upper in the neighborhood.
不过有点吵 隔壁有很多小孩
Hear the neighbors can be loud, though, lots of kids.
- 菲奥娜是个好女孩 - 是最好的
- Fiona's a good girl. - The best.
我们从小就认识
Known her since we were in Head Start.
很多年了
Long time, you know?
只要...小心驾车就好
Just... drive carefully.
你不会想因为开车受伤的
You don't want to get hurt down here.
嗯 这个真好吃
Mm, this is good.
我很好奇今晚在纯洁舞会
So, I'm just curious about what happens
到底都做些什么
at the Purity Ball tonight.
呃 这是一个基督教的活动 目的是
Well, it's a Christian event designed to
增强父女之间的亲情关系
strengthen the bond between fathers and daughters.
我们订立一个纯洁的契约 就像宣誓一样
We make a covenant of purity. Like an oath.
接下来我们交换承诺戒
And then we exchange promise rings
然后我们做一些贞洁的祷告
and, uh, we do some chastity prayers.
很有趣的
It's fun.
哇
Wow.
他们有没有给青年男子的这种舞会
Do they have these, um, balls for young men?
为什么要有
Why would they?
笑一个
Ready to smile?
哦 这一张太棒了
Aw. Oh, that's so nice!
太漂亮了
It's beautiful.
再来一张 再来一张
One more, one more.
太有爱了
It's so nice.
噢耶
Oh, yeah!
嘿 你回来了
Hey, you're back!
那是当然
Oh, hell yeah.
给那个贾斯珀上了一课
Showed that Jasper a thing or two.
那个混蛋会求着我别去起诉他
Bastard's going to be begging me not to sue him.
给爷来杯好酒
Let us have a bottle of your good stuff.
我有钱要入账了
I've got some money coming.
等你死了 我去参加你的葬礼
You know, when you die, I'm gonna go to your funeral
我要唱首歌
and I'm gonna sing a song.
歌词是这样的 "我要有钱了..." 天呐
It goes, I got money coming  Oh boy.
猜你现在后悔没做结扎手术了吧
Bet you wish you'd had that vasectomy by now, huh?
我觉得你可能想知道卡尔没有大碍
Just thought you'd want to know Carl's all right.
他们把他的胳膊复位了
They re-set his arm.
对 所以请你坐在凳子上
Yeah, so please stay on your barstool,
继续喝酒吧
and just keep drinking.
嘿
Hey.
我们还是办正事吧
Let's just do what we came here to do.
如果你想要钱 我一点也没有
If you're looking for money, I don't have any yet.
你妈还没有签署我的理赔协议
Your mom still hasn't signed my settlement papers.
我不知道她整天都去哪
I don't know where she's been all day.
她去拿利亚姆的DNA检查结果了
She's been getting Liam's DNA results.
祝贺你 你还是父亲
Congratulations, you're still the father.
你说真的吗
Are you serious?
哦 我就知道那都是谣言
Ooh. I thought that was always a rumor
说什么盖拉格夫人跟那个萨克斯风手
about Nana Gallagher having an affair
有一腿
with that sax player.
向我保证你不会
Promise you won't sign anything
签署任何放弃抚养权的协议
forfeiting parental rights.
得了吧 你知道莫妮卡不是个好母亲
Come on! You know what a bad mother Monica is.
我只是假装让她以为她能带走他
I'm just letting her pretend that she can have him
这样我才能拿到我的理赔金
so I can get my settlement.
如果她不会就轻易放弃怎么办
What if she doesn't give up that easy?
不不不 这是一个双赢的情况
No, no, no, this is a win-win situation.
我是说 即使她带他走了一阵子
I mean, even if she takes him for just a little while,
她也会回来的
she'll be back.
哭诉自己自尊心低下
Crying about her low self-esteem,
或声称男孩有多么需要他的父亲
or how boys actually need their fathers,
再或者恐惧阴茎
or penis grief.
意思是说你大半夜的时候醒来
That's when you wake up in the middle of the night
看着身旁躺着的那个人 然后你说
and you look at the person next to you, and you say,
"谁来帮帮我 我刚刚干了一个小姐"
"Somebody help me! I just fucked a lady."
我从没求过你任何东西 从来没有
I've never asked you for anything. Ever.
拜托 能不能让我缓一缓
Oh, come on. Will you please give me some time with this?
我能搞定 只要别给我压力
I can do this, I, just don't pressure me.
我得走开了
I've gotta walk away.
什么
What?
如果我不走 非得痛扁他不可
If I don't walk away, I'm going to fucking hit him.
管他呢
What the hell?
该死
Fuck!
小黛比
Debs.
你要这么做 就不再是我们的父亲
If you do this, you are on your own,
我没开玩笑 我受够了 我走了
and I'm not kidding. I'm done. I'm gone.
胡说
Bullshit.
你永远也离不开那些猴孩子们
You'll never leave those monkeys,
你太爱他们了
you love them too much.
这群孩子啊
Kids.
在我们开始之前 我先说两句
Before we begin, let me just say
你们愿意净化身心 我们是多么自豪
how proud we are of your desire to re-purify.
我女儿们参加过这个仪式
My daughters participated, and now,
即使至今还是单身
although still single, are enjoying
但她的生活无比圣洁
very spirit-filled lives.
帕蒂
Patty?
你想不想起个头
Would you like to start?
去年我唱小曲那段时间
Last year when I was singing madrigal,
我开始和唱诗班的一个男孩约会
I started dating a boy in the choir.
他说我们在交往 但我们除了在排练厅亲热外
He said we were dating, but we never met outside of
我们没在外面见过面
our make-out sessions in the rehearsal hall.
我不断地让他摸我
I repeatedly let him touch me
透过我的衬衫和胸罩 摸我的胸部
on my breasts, through my shirt and bra.
然后有一次 我感觉到他的...
And once, I felt his...
他的棒棒碰我的腿
his rod touch my leg.
这太尴尬了
This is so embarrassing.
我不敢相信我居然让他那么做
I can't believe I let him do this.
- 我很抱歉 - 谢谢你 帕蒂
- I'm so sorry. - Thank you, Patty.
感谢你鼓起勇气
I want to thank you for your courage
直面自己对欲望的挣扎
to confront your struggles with desire.
谁是下一个
Who's next?
伊莱恩
Elaine?
大家好
Hi.
我叫伊莱恩
My name is Elaine,
我只碰过一个...
and I only touched one...
阴茎
penis.
只有那一次
Once.
如果我不这么做的话 他会用管子打我
If I didn't, I was going to get hit with a pipe.
上帝啊 你为何要让我的女儿成为
God, why did you let my daughter become a slave
肉体的奴隶
to the flesh?
不然就会挨铁管打的呀
I was going to get hit with a pipe!
所以律师的意思是你束手无策吗
So the lawyer said there's nothing you can do?
我们若上诉 可能适得其反 情况会更糟
If we sue, it could backfire. Make things worse.
天啊 这地方闻着全是老家伙哈里森的味道
Jesus. This place still smells like old man Harris.
莫妮卡想要干什么
What did Monica want?
她想让我们过去吃晚饭
She wants us to come over for dinner.
搞个家庭聚会什么的
Some kind of a family meeting.
家庭
Family?
真他妈的操蛋
Fucking load of shit.
你告诉她我们知道利亚姆是弗兰克的孩子吗
You told her we know Liam is Frank's?
说了
Yeah.
你有没有大麻
You have any pot?
我觉得如果我清醒着去见老妈
I think if I have to go see Mom conscious,
我说不定会动粗
I might actually commit a violent felony.
那可是很久以来
That's the first time
你第一次叫她老妈
in a long time I've heard you call her Mom.
我叫了吗
I did?
我不知道是否真把她当做过自己的老妈
I don't know if I ever really felt like she was my mom.
伊恩和我做了DNA测试
Ian and I got our DNA tests done.
为什么
Why?
我不知道 可能是对
I don't know, got excited
不是弗兰克的孩子这一想法比较兴奋吧
at the idea of not being Frank's, and
如果我们都不是他的孩子
if none of us are his, then
那么你成为我们的监护人
you'd have a much easier time becoming
也就会轻松很多
our legal guardians.
利普一个小时之后去取结果
Lip's gonna pick up the results in about an hour.
那么 但愿你们不是弗兰克的孩子吧
Well...here's to you not being Frank's.
我一直表现得不太淑女
My actions have been unladylike
像出于本能 对此我真的很抱歉
and base in nature, and for that I am truly sorry.
凯伦
Karen.
为了得到全身心的净化
In order for you to receive the full gift of purity,
你要尽可能的坦白
you need to be as honest as you can.
没事 宝贝
It's okay, sweetheart.
就说说都发生了什么
Just tell what happened.
那好吧
Um, well, okay.
我很小的时候就开始给人口交
I started having oral sex at a very young age,
大概是十三岁吧
maybe 13.
是和邻里的几个家伙
It was guys around the neighborhood...
起初是三四个
three or four at first
后来就不止三四个
and then, well, more than three or four.
直到八年级 我才又了真正的性行为
I didn't have intercourse until the eighth grade.
一开始我并不享受
I didn't like it at first,
但差不多六次的时候
but then around the sixth time,
我开始感觉很爽
it started to feel good,
相当爽
really good,
但我并不引以为傲
but I didn't feel good about it.
有几次我嗨翻的时候
Um, there was a few times where I got high
开始尝试男生女生
and started experimenting with guys and girls
一起搞
at the same time.
我觉得倒也算不上是群P
I wouldn't necessarily call it an orgy,
但的确放眼望去全是裸体
but there were a lot of naked body parts flying around,
让人觉得非常爽
which felt very good but kind of bad
但同时又很内疚
all at the same time.
后来有次在明蒂卡尔森家过夜
And then there was the time at Mindy Carlson's sleepover
我们一起去洗澡
when we all got in the shower
然后相互涂肥皂
and started soaping each other up,
后来她妈妈进来了 大吃一惊
and then her mom walked in and freaked out
因为她看到明蒂
when she saw Mindy in the shower with a big,
戴着一个粗大的黑色假阳具
black strap-on dildo.
你这个婊子
You whore!
婊子没有资格要车
Whores don't get cars!
好了
Okay.
来了 大家都饿了吧
There, I hope everybody's hungry.
快吃吧 伊恩 这是你最爱吃的
There you go, Ian, it's your favorite.
这是什么
What is it?
意大利千层面啊
Lasagna.
卡尔 你能把沙拉递过来吗
Carl, could you start passing the salad, please?
莫妮卡是利亚姆的生母
Monica is Liam's mother,
- 我知道你们会不高兴 但是 - 老天
- and I know you won't be happy, but... - Jesus,
鲍比 我们不能开开心心用餐 饭后再谈
Bob, can we just enjoy our dinner and then talk after...?
谈什么
Talk about what?
黛比
Debbie,
拜托
please.
利普呢
Where's Lip?
他有事
Had something to do.
他不来吗
He's not coming?
抱歉 我回来晚了
Sorry I-I'm late.
还有吃的吗
Did I miss the chow?
看上去不错啊
Ooh... looks good.
如果你把我们都叫过来是要告诉我们
If you called us here to tell us
你要带走利亚姆并再次离开的话
that you're taking Liam and leaving again,
我们不想听
we don't want to hear it.
菲奥娜 你不爽 我明白
Fiona, you're upset, I get it.
我嫁给弗兰克十八年了
I was married to Frank for 18 years.
我明白 每天就像在生吞玻璃渣
I know, it's like swallowing broken glass every day.
利普 太好了 我们刚开饭
Oh, Lip, wonderful. We just started.
你妈妈跟你说六点半开饭
Your mother said 6:30.
你手表丢了吗
You lose your watch?
我没有手表 鲍比
I don't have a watch, Bob.
什么结果
What's the news?
还没打开 我觉得我们应该一起看
Haven't opened it yet. Figured we should do it together.
谢谢
Thanks.
我跟伊恩决定也去做个DNA鉴定
Me and Ian decided to get our DNA tests done, too,
真希望我们不是弗兰克的孩子啊
on the off chance that maybe we aren't Frank's kids.
什么
What?
你和鲍比测得那么开心
Yeah. We figured why should you and Bob
我们也玩玩
get to have all the fun?
我靠
Holy shit.
恭喜你 伊恩
Congratulations, Ian.
你不是弗兰克盖拉格的儿子
You are not Frank Gallagher's son.
妈的
Fuck!
凯伦
Karen?
宝贝儿
Sweetie...
甜心
Honey?
宝贝 你这么快就从舞会上回来了
Sweetie, you're back from the ball so soon?
亲爱的
Honey?
凯伦
Karen?
还许诺要他妈的给我辆车
He promised me the fucking car!
凯伦 亲爱的 怎么回事
Karen, sweetie, what's going on?
还说为我感到骄傲
I'm so proud of you!
什么你让我想起我第一次的圣餐仪式
You remind me of my first communion!
他竟然羞辱我
He humiliated me!
他让我以为他是爱我的
He made me think he loved me!
坦白说 宝贝
Honestly, sweetie,
我不知道
I don't know.
1995年夏天有那么一周
There was that week in the summer of '95
我嗑了很多天使粉
that I did a lot of PCP.
- 然后我 - 你嗑了天使粉
- And I... - You did PCP?
不带上我吗
Without me?!
你保证过我们要一起嗑的
You promised we would do that together!
打断一下 能不能回到谁是伊恩生父的问题上
Excuse me. Can we get back to who Ian's father is?
莫妮卡背着弗兰克偷情 这挺好
I like the idea of Monica cheating on Frank, you know?
这让我对你的好印象得以保留 老妈
It really keeps my image of you right on track, Mom.
有没有人能告诉我
Will somebody please tell me
我们在谈论什么呢
what we're talking about?
好吧 结果表明
All right, the results say
你 弗兰克 铁定不是我亲生父亲
that you, Frank, are absolutely not my father.
但我生父是你的亲戚
But my father is a close relative,
非常可能是你的一个兄弟
most likely one of your brothers.
爸爸还有兄弟吗
Dad has brothers?
有两个是吧
He has two, right?
三个
Three.
我见过的那个兄弟
You know, I think I met the one
是用汽车的后备箱
that sells smoked sausage and razor blades
卖熏肠和剃须刀片的
out of the trunk of his car.
好吧
All right.
我真不知道
I-I honestly don't know.
我们还是一家人吗
Are we still related?
你们当然是啊
Of course you are.
你不但背着我嗑天使粉
Not only did you lie to me about the PCP,
还上了我的兄弟 接下来是什么
you fucked my brother! What's next?
你是不是还准备找一个黑人女爷们儿
You gonna take up with a black lady/man?
我忘了 你已经找了一个
Oh, I forgot, that's already happened.
现在我们还怎么复合
How can we get back together now?
我从来都没想过
I have never, ever had any intention of getting back
要跟你复合 弗兰克
together with you, Frank.
看在老天的份上 你把我骗回来
For Chrissake, you only tricked me into coming here
就是想拿到那笔理赔金
to get some settlement money!
我也想见见你
I wanted to see you again.
所以你就骗她赢了个泰迪熊吗
So you pretended that she won a teddy bear?
你知道我有多爱泰迪熊
You know how much I love teddy bears.
你跟莫妮卡完了 弗兰克
You and Monica are over, Frank.
我跟莫妮卡就要结婚了
Me and Monica are getting married.
扯淡 她还没跟我离婚呢
Aah! She's still married to me.
快了 她要跟你离婚
Not for long. She's getting a divorce.
你们俩还没离婚吗
You two are still married?
两个女人怎么结婚
How can two ladies get married?
他们是同性恋
They're lesbians.
不插入也可以做爱
Penetration isn't required for sex to occur.
怎么 现在许多州同性结婚都是合法的
What? It's legal now in several states.
离了吧 弗兰克
Divorce, Frank.
这个是你欠她的
You owe her at least that much.
那她欠我的怎么还
What about what she owes me?!
她还要再次把六个孩子留给我吗
She gonna leave me again with six kids?
让我来处理这堆烂摊子
Leave me to deal with all the shit?
应该说又把这烂摊子交给我了吧
You mean leave me to deal with the shit.
我没有抛弃你
I didn't leave you!
是你把我逼走的
You drove me out!
任何有自尊的人都不会和你在一起 弗兰克
No self-respecting person could stay with you, Frank!
- 你待我就像对待一只狗 - 你
- You treated me like a dog! - You...
你得让我们来抚养利亚姆
You need to let us raise Liam.
我才不管亲子鉴定结果是什么
I don't care what the test results say.
利亚姆应该跟我们生活在一起
Liam belongs with us!
谁也不能带走利亚姆
Nobody's taking Liam!
真不敢相信你竟然想和我离婚
I can't believe you want a divorce.
我和鲍比值得拥有自己的家庭
Me and Bob deserve a family of our own.
你已经有个家庭了 只不过你抛弃了而已
You had a family! You left it!
我没想离开你们 是他逼我的
I didn't leave you! He drove me out!
你本该留下来保护我们的
You should have protected us!
我尽力了 可是我办不到
I tried, but I couldn't!
菲奥娜 如果我没走 我早就死了
Fiona, if I didn't leave, I would have died!
别胡扯了 莫娜罗伊
Oh, cut the shit, Myrna Loy.
电影中的好老婆形象
你们根本不知道跟他过日子是什么样
You have no idea what it was like being married to him.
你们也不知道我们的婚姻有多糟糕
You have no idea how bad it is!
是吗 说说看
Yeah? Try me.
别胡扯了
Oh, come on now!
我知道他曾经折磨过你
Okay, I know that he tortured you.
我知道他毁了你
I know that he ruined you,
但嫁给他的人可不是我们 妈妈
but we didn't marry him, Mom.
是你
You did.
如果你爱我们 不管是爱哪一个 爱多少
If you love us, any of us in any way,
你都会留下利亚姆 带上你的女朋友
you'll leave Liam, take your girlfriend,
坐上你们的卡车 再也别回来了
get in your truck and never come back.
可是
But...
我
I...
我爱你们
I love you...
真的
I do.
妈的
Shit.
你到底是怎么回事
What's the matter with you?
她跟你说了吗
She tell you?
她告诉你她说了些什么吗
She tell you what she said?
你竟然骂我们的女儿是婊子
You called our daughter a whore.
怎么不说说她是怎么对我的呢
How about what she did to me?!
滚出去 滚
Get out. Out.
- 什么 - 快滚
- What...? - Just get out!
- 滚出去 - 她跟你说她是怎么对我的吗
- Get out! - Did she mention what she did to me?!
- 你明不明白 - 快滚
- You understand? - Get out!
她也是个人
She's a human being!
她应该被爱 而不是厌恶
She deserves love, not hate!
你没在场 全都是熟人
You weren't there. I know all those people?
你有什么毛病 再也别回来了
What's the matter with you?! Don't ever come back!
- 你们就继续鬼混吧 - 别再回来了 滚
- Just keep going on and on! - Don't ever come back! Go!
快滚 再也别回来了
Get out! Don't ever come back!
永远别回来
Forever!
弗兰克 你知道埃迪对我的凯伦做了什么吗
Frank! Frank, did you see what Eddie did to my Karen?
你走出家门了
You're out of the house.
什么
What?
你在房子外面了
You're out of the house.
我 我
I-I...
我气疯了 我就冲出来了
I got so mad, I-I-I came out of the house.
我走出来了 我终于走出来了
I'm out of the house! I'm out of the house!
弗兰克
Frank!
看看我 大家好
Look at me! Hello!
她们在做什么
What are they doing?
像是在打包
Looks like packing.
利亚姆呢
What about Liam?
隔着窗户看不清
I can't tell through the window.
我们可以报警
We could call the police.
告诉他们利亚姆被绑架了
Tell 'em Liam's being kidnapped.
我们会把这烂事搞定的
Hey, we're gonna figure this shit out, okay?
无论如何
No matter what.
伙计们 他们出来了
Hey, guys, they-they're coming out.
妈妈
Mom?
还有盖拉格夫人
And Mrs. Gallagher.
盖拉格夫人 你的名字怎么读啊
Mrs. Gallagher, how do you pronounce your first name?
莫妮卡
Monica.
莫卡 莫卡
Monka. Monka.
- 是莫妮卡 - 莫卡
- Monica. - Monka.
哈尔?
清出去
Out.
等等 等等
Wait-wait-wait!
你们不能这样 那是我的钱啊
You-you can't do that! That's my money!
那是 等等 是我的钱
That is... Wait a second! That's my money!
妈的 给你吹箫啥也没捞着
I blow you for nothing!
下一位
Next.